(Penny:)You two want to be alone?
(Leonard:)I want you to know I get
why you don't want the money--
(Leonard:)you've got this new job,
you're excited
(Leonard:)about being financially
independent--
(Leonard:)and I am nothing
but proud of you.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you so much.
(Penny:)It feels so good
to hear you say that.
(Penny:)And I want you
to know
(Penny:)that I get this job
kind of changes
(Penny:)the balance in our relationship,
(Penny:)and... I'm trying
to be sensitive to that.
(Penny:)What?
(Penny:)Well, I just think that
maybe you're a little hung up
(Penny:)on the money because
I'm less reliant on you now,
(Penny:)and that's a little scary.
(Leonard:)Hmm.
(Bernadette:)Maybe.
Or maybe I tried
to do something nice
(Leonard:)and maybe you had
a problem with it
(Leonard:)because of your control issues.
(Penny:)Control issues?
(Bernadette:)Maybe.
Or... maybe...
(Penny:)now that I'm no longer
an out-of-work actress
(Penny:)who can't pay
for her own dinner,